<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
			 xmlns:p='urn:import:com.fave100.client.pages'>
             
    <ui:style src="../../../client/resources/css/global.css" type="com.fave100.client.resources.css.GlobalStyle">
    	.container h1 {
			margin-top: 30px;
			margin-bottom: 60px;
			text-align: center;
    	}
    	
    	.container h2 {
			margin-bottom: 10px;
    	}
    	
    	.container img {
			padding: 15px;
			max-width: 100%;
			height: auto;
    	}
    	    	
    	.container > div {
			margin-bottom: 50px;
			overflow: hidden;
    	}
    	
    	.container > div > div {
			padding: 15px;
			overflow: hidden;
			min-width: 300px;
    	}
    	
    	.container p {
			margin-bottom: 10px;
			font-size: 17px;
			line-height: 28px;
    	}
    	
    	.imageLeft {			
			float: left;
    	}
    	
    	.imageRight {
			float: right;
    	}
    </ui:style>
    
    <ui:with field="img" type="com.fave100.client.resources.img.ImageResources" />
    
    <p:Page ui:field="page">
		<p:content>
			<g:HTMLPanel ui:styleName="{style.container} {style.paddedMainPage}">
						
						<h1>Ranking your music has never been easier</h1>
			
						<g:FlowPanel>
							<g:Image ui:styleName="{style.imageLeft}" ui:resource="{img.aboutScreen1}"></g:Image>
							<g:HTMLPanel>
								<h2>List-based music discovery</h2>
								<p>Fave100 is a music discovery site that asks the simple question: if you could only recommend 5, 10, 50 or even 100 songs, what would they be? And, in what order?</p>
								<p>Our Home Page displays the all-time Fave100 based on everyone’s lists so far. You can also create other lists based on genre (e.g. classicrock), 
									year (e.g 2013), event (e.g. micksparty) or whatever else comes to mind.
								</p>							
							</g:HTMLPanel>
						</g:FlowPanel>
						
						<g:FlowPanel>
							<g:Image ui:styleName="{style.imageRight}" ui:resource="{img.aboutScreen2}"></g:Image>
							<g:HTMLPanel>
								<h2>Personalized, shareable lists</h2>
								<p>Your personal Fave100 page is your own customized countdown, fully ranked and ready to share with the world. </p>
								<p>And each pick asks for an optional Why-Line, a 90 character or less answer to the question: “Why is this one of your favourites?”</p>
								<p>Follow friends, journalists, celebrities or anyone else whose musical taste piques your interest.</p>
							</g:HTMLPanel>
						</g:FlowPanel>
					
						<g:FlowPanel>
							<g:Image ui:styleName="{style.imageLeft}" ui:resource="{img.aboutScreen3}"></g:Image>
							<g:HTMLPanel>
								<h2>Over 9 million songs</h2>
								<p>Building your list is a breeze, thanks to our robust database of over 9 million songs. You can search by artist or song title or both. </p>
								<p>Also, you can add songs from other lists to your list with the click of a button.</p>
							</g:HTMLPanel>
						</g:FlowPanel>
					
						<g:FlowPanel>
							<g:Image ui:styleName="{style.imageRight}" ui:resource="{img.aboutScreen4}"></g:Image>
							<g:HTMLPanel>
								<h2>Rank with ease</h2>
								<p>Editing your list is easy and intuitive. Use arrows to move a pick up or down the list or simply click on a ranking number to quickly change its position.</p>
								<p>To edit a Why-Line, simply click on it and enter your changes. Creating a ranked music list has never been easier.</p>
							</g:HTMLPanel>
						</g:FlowPanel>
					
						<g:FlowPanel>
							<g:Image ui:styleName="{style.imageLeft}" ui:resource="{img.aboutScreen5}"></g:Image>
							<g:HTMLPanel>
								<h2>Sit back and enjoy</h2>
								<p>Click on any song, sit back and enjoy the sights and sounds. What’s more, the entire list where that song appears will play continuously.</p>
								<p>You can also see featured Why-Lines as well as others who have that song in their list. There is simply no end to the amount of music discovery you can enjoy at Fave100!</p>
								<p>So, what are you waiting for? Get your list on today!</p>
							</g:HTMLPanel>
						</g:FlowPanel>
					
				</g:HTMLPanel>
		</p:content>
	</p:Page>
    
</ui:UiBinder>
